<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>



			

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title><![CDATA[New Videos]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/latest-updates/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:51:53 IST</lastBuildDate>
	<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Chubby Bangla girlfriend Rehana's big boobs sucking by bf
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/chubby-bangla-girlfriends-big-boobs-sucking-by-bf/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/chubby-bangla-girlfriends-big-boobs-sucking-by-bf/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2710/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;Watch the horny guy not sparing his beautiful Bangladeshi girlfriend's big boobs, once they were out of her top. The bf kisses the young and chubby Bangla babe Rehana briefly, before squeezing her big melons and taking them in his mouth. He enjoys sucking the soft tits and hard nipples, all this while smartly arousing the busty girl and convincing her to have sex.&lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:30:53 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/chubby-bangla-girlfriends-big-boobs-sucking-by-bf/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Lucky UP guy fucks neighbour's daughter when everyone busy
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/lucky-up-guy-fucks-neighbours-daughter-sneakily/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/lucky-up-guy-fucks-neighbours-daughter-sneakily/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2706/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;Watch the Meerut bachelor guy getting himself into a risky sex encounter with his neighbour's daughter during daytime when the street was fully alive with people. After sneaking in the neighbour's daughter to his room without anyone noticing, he slowly undresses her while spending some time on her boobs and pussy to arouse her. After removing the UP girl's underwear, the bachelor rubs and fingers her already precum-oozing chut for a while. Once she was in the mood, the young North Indian girl hungrily sucks the guy's hanging dick for several minutes before inserting it into her pussy to have fulfilling sex. &lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:00:00 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/lucky-up-guy-fucks-neighbours-daughter-sneakily/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Tired Pakistani Punjabi wife Shazia hot, second round fucking
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/tired-pakistani-punjabi-wife-shazia-hot-second-round-fucking/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/tired-pakistani-punjabi-wife-shazia-hot-second-round-fucking/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2704/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;The chubby, Pakistani wife Shazia was a little exhausted after the first round of sex. However, her horny partner, who was in the mood for another round, quickly got in between his busty Punjabi biwi's thick legs. As he starts licking and sucking the tired pussy intensely, the Paki woman slowly gets aroused and moans sexily. Once Shazia also got in the mood for the second round, the guy climbs over her and fucks her hard with all his remaining energy hard in missionary position till he cums inside her again.&lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:30:00 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/tired-pakistani-punjabi-wife-shazia-hot-second-round-fucking/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Unsatisfied Bengali bhabhi's secret affair with college neighbour
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/unsatisfied-bengali-bhabhis-secret-affair-college-neighbour/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/unsatisfied-bengali-bhabhis-secret-affair-college-neighbour/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2703/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;The Kharagpur boudi, who was left fully horny for almost 2 years by her husband as he went to work abroad, fulfills her sexual desires secretly through her young and hormone-raging neighbour. Meanwhile, the college guy in his Bengali neighbour bhabhi's bedroom, takes his time to make sure that she is pleasured well enough to continue this secret affair. After kissing the bhabhi passionately, the youngster focuses his full attention on the married Bengali woman's huge boobs, sucking them very nicely and enjoying the foreplay before the intercourse. &lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:00:00 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/unsatisfied-bengali-bhabhis-secret-affair-college-neighbour/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Chubby desi wife hairy chut fingered and fucked at night
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/chubby-desi-wife-hairy-chut-fingered-and-fucked-at-night/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/chubby-desi-wife-hairy-chut-fingered-and-fucked-at-night/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2709/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;The chubby, desi wife initially wanted to just sleep, but her horny husband warms up her hairy chut and her whole body by inserting his fingers and finger-fucking it. As the nude, big boobs woman grows hornier, she starts moving her body up and down in pleasure. After a  few seconds, her husband pushes his thick lund into her hairy pussy and slowly fucks her that night briefly before sleeping. &lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:30:46 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/chubby-desi-wife-hairy-chut-fingered-and-fucked-at-night/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Houseowner's beautiful daughter seduced & fucked sensually
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/houseowners-beautiful-daughter-seduced-fucked-sensually/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/houseowners-beautiful-daughter-seduced-fucked-sensually/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2700/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;The 20-year-old, beautiful Indian college girl's horny tenant guy finally succeeded in seducing her. And one day, after seeing the houseowner and his wife leaving for a wedding in the next city, the tenant guy makes his move and eventually ends up getting in bed with the most innocent girl of his dreams. The guy guides the houseowner's nude daughter to blow his dick multiple times and then pushes her to the bed and fucks her sensually for as long as he can, in the video.&lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:00:00 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/houseowners-beautiful-daughter-seduced-fucked-sensually/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Newly married Arab couple raw honeymoon sex mms in Dubai
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/newly-married-arab-couple-raw-honeymoon-sex-mms-dubai/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/newly-married-arab-couple-raw-honeymoon-sex-mms-dubai/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2699/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;Watch the freshly-wedded Arab couple's intense fucking video on their honeymoon. After inserting his hard cock into the tight pussy hole of his sexy Dubai wife Amna, the husband waits for a minute, kissing and smooching her to ease her tension a bit. After the short wait, the UAE man starts stroking slowly at first and suddenly picks up the speed. As the Arab hubby fucks the brains out of his beautiful wife, she moans loudly in that large house. At the end, the man pulls out just before cumming, and sprays his semen on his Arab wife's face and neck.&lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:30:00 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/newly-married-arab-couple-raw-honeymoon-sex-mms-dubai/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Sexy maal American girlfriend gives blowjob to Indian BF
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/sexy-maal-american-girlfriend-gives-blowjob-to-indian-bf/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/sexy-maal-american-girlfriend-gives-blowjob-to-indian-bf/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2697/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;Watch the sexy American girl and her NRI boyfriend having some oral fun before the main intercourse. The hot USA girlfriend with her big and gorgeous boobs out of her top takes her Indian lover's hard cock in her mouth. Cupping his balls softly, the Western redhead chick blows the wood like a pro and stops only after getting the taste of the guy's cum in her mouth. &lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:00:00 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/sexy-maal-american-girlfriend-gives-blowjob-to-indian-bf/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Lusty desi Pune bhabhi riding ex-lover's dick at his place (no sound)
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/lusty-desi-pune-bhabhi-riding-ex-lovers-dick-his-place/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/lusty-desi-pune-bhabhi-riding-ex-lovers-dick-his-place/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2705/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;Check out the secret fucking video of a desi bhabhi from Pune. After her ex-boyfriend unexpectedly moved into her neighbourhood, the married bhabhi couldn't quite control her lust because of the steamy sexual history they had in the past. The lust got the better of the Indian bhabhi as she visited her ex-lover's house one day when her husband was on a business trip and eventually ended up bouncing on her old flame's lund with her horny pussy. The married woman forgets everything elseand gradually enjoys the hot cowgirl sex with ex.&lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:30:40 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/lusty-desi-pune-bhabhi-riding-ex-lovers-dick-his-place/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Busy Kolkata housewife pulled into bed & fucked passionately
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/busy-kolkata-housewife-pulled-bed-fucked-passionately/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/busy-kolkata-housewife-pulled-bed-fucked-passionately/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2696/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;The dusky Bengali wife had so much work to do in the house in the morning, but her horny husband, who didn't have office that day. Without warning, he pulls her to the bed and starts giving her a quick drilling after getting rid of her clothes. After the initial minute of hesitation, the traditional Kolkata housewife couldn't help but enjoy as her hubby's warm rod was thrusting continuously into her pussy. The married Bengali woman embraces her partner tightly, closes her eyes, and fully melts herself in the passionate sex.&lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:00:00 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/busy-kolkata-housewife-pulled-bed-fucked-passionately/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Hot Filipino college girl allows teacher to fuck her for grades
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/hot-filipino-college-girl-allows-teacher-to-fuck-for-grades/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/hot-filipino-college-girl-allows-teacher-to-fuck-for-grades/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2695/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;The Pinay college babe couldn't afford to fail in the internal assessment of her main subject and decided to bring her teacher, who always used to stare at her sexy figure, on her side. At the professor's place on a weekend, the Filipino college girl makes her intention very clear and soon finds herself lying fully naked on his bed and getting fucked in her sexy pussy hard with the thick dick. What started as a sex for good grades, soon becomes more pleasurable than expected for the big boobs Asian girl in the video.&lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:30:00 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/hot-filipino-college-girl-allows-teacher-to-fuck-for-grades/</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title><![CDATA[
		Old Sarpanch screwing Bihari village wife when husband away
	]]></title>
	<link>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/old-sarpanch-screwing-bihari-village-wife-when-husband-away/</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
		<a href="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/old-sarpanch-screwing-bihari-village-wife-when-husband-away/"><img src="https://www.desitales2.com/videos/contents/videos_screenshots/2000/2694/320x180/1.jpg" border="0"><br>&lt;div&gt;Watch the old village head from Basantpur managing to fuck a mature village housewife after sending her husband away to get some things done. Soon after the Bihari rural village wife sets the bed and pillow on the floor and lies down, the horny Sarpanch quickly comes in between the married woman's open legs, inserts his dick into her pussy, and fucks her with continuous strokes.&lt;/div&gt;</a>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:00:00 IST</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.desitales2.com/videos/old-sarpanch-screwing-bihari-village-wife-when-husband-away/</guid>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>